Guide to the Academic Personnel Office records,1980-1984.
Academic Personnel Office records, 1980-1984
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Academic Personnel Office records, 1980-1984.
10-3-2531
Cornell University. Academic Personnel Office.
2 cubic ft.
Files.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Files concerning promotions of the Executive Committee and Board of Trustees.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Files concerning promotions of the Executive Committee and Board of Trustees.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. Academic Personnel Office.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of office of origin.
CONTAINER LIST
- Executive Committee, July 1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Executive Committee, Sept. 1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Executive Committee, Oct. 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Board of Trustees, Oct. 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Executive Committee, Nov. 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Executive Committee, Dec. 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Board of Trustees, Jan. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Executive Committee, Jan. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Executive Committee, Mar. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Board of Trustees, Mar. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Executive Committee, May 1981 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Executive Committee, May 1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Executive Committee, May 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Executive Committee, July 1981 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Executive Committee, Oct. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Board of Trustees, Oct. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Executive Committee, Dec. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Executive Committee, Jan. 1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Board of Trustees, Jan. 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Executive Committee, Mar. 1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Board of Trustees, Mar. 1982 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Executive Committee, Apr. 1982 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Executive Committee, May 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Board of Trustees, May 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24.1)
- Board of Trustees, May 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24.2)
- Executive Committee, July 1982 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Executive Committee, Sept. 1982 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Executive Committee, Oct. 1982 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Board of Trustees, Oct. 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Executive Committee, Dec. 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Executive Committee, Jan. 1983 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Board of Trustees, Jan. 1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Executive Committee, Mar. 1983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Board of Trustees, Mar. 1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Executive Committee, Apr. 1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Executive Committee, May 1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Board of Trustees, May 1983 (Box 2, Folder 9.1)
- Board of Trustees, May 1983 (Box 2, Folder 9.2)
- Executive Committee, July 1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Board of Trustees, Oct. 1983 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Executive Committee, Dec. 1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Board of Trustees, Jan. 1984 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Board of Trustees, Mar. 1984 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Executive Committee, Apr. 1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Board of Trustees, May 1984 (Box 2, Folder 16.1)
- Board of Trustees, May 1984 (Box 2, Folder 16.2)
- Executive Committee, July 1984 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Executive Committee, Sept. 1984 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Board of Trustees, Oct. 1984 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Executive Committees, Dec. 1984 (Box 2, Folder 20)